On 17 November 2007 a man was jailed for producing works of art.
2007年11月17日，一名男子因创作艺术品而被判入狱。
Why?
为什么呢？
Because the sculptures and artefacts Shaun Greenhalgh made were fakes: fakes that had conned museums and galleries out of over £500,000.
因为肖恩・格林哈尔格制作的雕塑和手工艺品都是赝品：这些赝品骗走了博物馆和美术馆超过50万英镑。
Shaun had left school with no qualifications, but tried his hand at a wide range of crafts – from watercolour painting to sculpture.
肖恩离开学校时没有任何学历资质，但他尝试了各种各样的手工艺——从水彩画到雕塑。
The young Greenhalgh hoped to make it as an artist himself.
年轻的格林哈尔格曾希望自己能成为一名艺术家。
His pieces were not admired, however, and he turned to forgery.
然而，他的作品无人欣赏，于是他转向了伪造艺术品。
He ended up creating a cottage industry in his garden shed, with the help of his family.
最终，在家人的帮助下，他在自家花园的小棚子里搞起了家庭作坊手工业。
If the son had a talent for art, his father, George, had the gift of the gab and approached potential buyers.
如果说儿子有艺术天赋，那么他的父亲乔治则有找到潜在买家的口才天赋。
He came up with detailed stories about how he found artworks which had been lost for generations.
他编造出详细的故事，讲述自己是如何发现那些失传了好几代的艺术品的。
In 2003, they sold a 50cm statue called the 'Amarna Princess' to Bolton Museum.
2003年，他们把一尊50厘米高名为“阿马尔奈公主”的雕像卖给了博尔顿博物馆。
George claimed his own grandfather had bought it at an auction in 1892 at an aristocrat's home, and had papers which appeared to back up his story.
乔治声称他的祖父在1892年于一位贵族家中的拍卖会上买下了这尊雕像，并且还有文件似乎能证实他的说法。
After talking to art experts, the museum paid more than £400,000 for the statue.
在与艺术专家沟通后，博物馆花了超过40万英镑买下了这尊雕像。
The successful scam made the forgers grow bolder.
这次成功的骗局让这些造假者胆子更大了。
But when they approached the British Museum with some more fake artefacts, an expert spotted mistakes and tipped off the police.
但当他们带着更多的赝品文物找到大英博物馆时，一位专家发现了破绽并向警方报了信。
After 18 months of investigations, the police knocked at the family's door.
经过18个月的调查，警方敲响了这家人的家门。
They were surprised by the Greenhalgh's humble home.
格林哈尔格一家简陋的住所让他们倍感惊讶。
Where were the riches of successful criminals?
成功罪犯的财富都到哪里去了呢？
The police concluded that Shaun was motivated by "a resentment of the art market" and by a desire to deceive art experts, rather than by money.
警方得出结论，肖恩这么做的动机是“对艺术市场的不满”以及想要欺骗艺术专家，而非为了钱财。
But how did he manage to fool so many experts?
但是他是如何成功骗过这么多专家的呢？
Irvin Finkel from the British Museum says the family produced things that "in a way we were looking for already".
大英博物馆的欧文・芬克尔说，这家人制作的东西“在某种程度上正是我们一直在寻找的”。
So when experts saw them they wanted to embrace these apparently long-lost treasures.
所以当专家们看到这些东西时，他们就想要接纳这些看似失传已久的珍宝。